A Guide to the Charles Burchard Collection, 1935-1989, n.d.
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Series II: College of Architecture, Program & Curriculum, 1959-1987, n.d.
  Subseries C: Brochures, Booklets, & Student Work, 1965-1982, n.d., includes works and project created by students of Burchard (models, negatives, photographs), booklets and pamphlets about the programs in the college (as well as resources used to generate booklets), and items relating to the construction and dedication of Cowgill Hall.
  Subseries D: General Curriculum Materials, 1964-1980, contains notes, statistics about the college, documentation on the early 1970s reorganization, information on degree programs and courses, and programs abroad. This subseries is organized alphabetically by folder title (subject).
  Subseries E: Administrative Materials, 1959-1987, consists of papers and files relating to the day-to-day and managerial aspects of the College of Architecture. This includes administrative correspondence, notes from committee meetings, files and programs from events, newspaper clippings, and recommendation letters. This subseries is organized into sub-groups by type of material. Within each sub-group, folders are in chronological order.
  - Subseries A: Proposals & Studies, 1961-1980
    - VPI: New Building for Architecture Deptartment, 1961-1965 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Report: Symposium on Campus Planning & Design, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Curriculum: Landscape Architecture, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Study of the Profession of Landscape Architecture (2 folders), 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 32-33)
    - Landscape Architecture Libraries & Collections Development, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Study of the Profession of Landscape Architecture (2 folders), 1970-1972 (Box 8, Folder 35-36)
    - A Study of the Profession of Landscape Architecture (3 Books), 1972 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Proposed New Degree Program, Doctor of Environmental Design and Planning, College of Architecture, VPISU, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - A Direction for the Seventies-Drafts (4 folders), 1974 (Box 9, Folder 4-7)
    - Proposal for CAUS Meeting Space, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - VPI Long Range Planning Data, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - CAUS Position Proposals, 1978-1980 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Landscape Architecture Accreditation, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - VPI: Report of the Blueprint Committee on Athletics, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Curriculum & Program Proposals (5 folders) (Box 9, Folder 9-13)
    - Proposal for Master of Architecture in Environmental Systems (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Reports: Planning and Study Committee, College of Architecture, Virginia Polytechnic Institute, c.1865? (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Subseries B: VPI College of Architecture Self Studies & NAAB Accreditation Materials, 1959-1980
    - NAAB Comments, 1959-1966 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - NAAB Evaluation of the Department of Architecture at VPI, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - College of Architecture Self-Study, 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - College of Architecture, Report for NAAB, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - College of Architecture Long Range Plan, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - College of Architecure Long Range Plan, 1970-1972 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - NAAB Restructoring, Misc. Notes, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Education Development Plan, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - EDP Handbook, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - NAAB Restructuring (2 folders), 1974-1976 (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
    - NAAB, EDP, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - NAAB Meeting, March 7-8, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - CAUS Self-Study, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - CAUS Educational Development Plan, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - NAAB, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - NAAB Misc., 1975-1978 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - NAAB Handbooks, 1975-1979 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - NAAB Accreditation Evaluation Conference, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - SACS Report & Self Study, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - NAAB Accreditattion Report, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Education Development Plan, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - CAUS Accreditation, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - NAAB, Accredited Programs Architecture, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - ACSA, Accreditation Survey, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - NAAB Criteria & Procedures, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - NAAB Self-Study Materials, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Subseries C: Brochures, Booklets, & Student Work, 1965-1982, n.d.
    - Architecture Models: Prints, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Architecture Models: Negatives and Proofs, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Student Projects, City Center for Learning, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - College of Architecture: Student Publications, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Booklets: Graduate Environmental Systems Studies, 1969-1973 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Dedication of Cowgill Hall, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Cowgill Hall & Old H.S. Building, Charles Worley, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Cowgill Hall Photographs, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Mounted Photographs: Cowgill & Blacksburg, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Mounted Photographs: Foundation Student Work, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Booklets: COA Foundation Division, 1970-1981 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Notes from First Year Architecture Student, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Booklets: COA Programs, 1975-1982 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Booklets: College of Architecture & Urban Studies, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Original Diagram Drawing (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Student Projects: The Urban Scale (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Student Work (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Subseries D: General Curriculum Materials, 1964-1980
    - Architecture Workbook, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Architecture Curriculum: Notes & Revisions, 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Charles Burchard Notes, VPI (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - COA: Curriculum & Graduate Structure, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - College of Architecture: Curriculum Notes & Diagrams (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - College of Architecture: Growth Estimation, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - College of Architecture: Proposed Ten Year Growth, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - CAUS Reorganization, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - College Framework Notes, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Curriculum: Architecture, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Curriculum Diagrams & School Heirachy Board, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - The EDPM Tetrahedron (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Honors Seminar Notes (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - M. Architecture/Urban Design New Directions, FFE, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Miscellaneous Curriculum, 1968-1980 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Curriculum (con't.), 1968-1980 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Policy & Coordination Council Meeting Notes (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Progressive Architecture, CAUS Curriculum, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Resource Documentation (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Rethinking & Methodologies of Process (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Revision Worksheets for Architecture Curriculum (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Revisions of the Architecture Curriculum, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Salzbury, Austria, Undergraduate Summer Program, 1968-1973 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Student Talks Notes, VPI (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Summer Orientation Talk Notes, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - VPI Architecture Curriculum (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Writings & Reports on Curriculum & Education (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Subseries E: Administrative Materials, 1959-1987
    - Administrative Correspondence
      - VPI, Department of Architecture to Charles Burchard, 1959-1963 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - Charles Worley to Charles Burchard, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 20)
      - Faculty Salaries & Stipends, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 24)
      - Charles Burchard, Letter to Graduates & List, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 26)
      - University Correspondence & Meeting Minutes (2 folders), 1979-1981 (Box 11, Folder 40-41)
      - Administration Memorandums, 1979-1985 (Box 11, Folder 43)
      - Student Travel Aboard, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Committees & Boards
      - Education Innovation for Architectureal Technologies, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 23)
      - PDP 8/I Computer, Decus, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 28)
      - PDP 8/I Computer, Decus (con't), 1975 (Box 11, Folder 29)
      - VA Foundation for Architectural Education, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 39)
      - CAUS: Washington Alexandria Center, 1980-1982 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - CAUS: Biennium, 1980-1982 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Advisory Council, Princton School of Architecture, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Global Issues, Advisory Board, 1982-1984 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - CAUS Advisory Council, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Events
      - VPI 107th Annual commencement 1979 (Box 11, Folder 35)
      - Celebration for Charles Burchard's Retirement, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Newspaper Clippings
      - Newspaper Clippings: VPI, College of Architecture Dean Appointment, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 19)
      - Newspaper Articles: VPI Puplicity, 1965-1980 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Other Universities
      - Iowa State College of Design Consultation, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 38)
      - Iowa State College of Design, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 37)
      - University of Wisconsin at Milwauke (2 folders), 1980 (Box 11, Folder 44, Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Recommendation Letters
      - Letters of Recommendation, 1960-1986 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - Letters of Commendation, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 27)
      - CAUS Promotion Recommendations, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 30)
      - Caus Promotion Recommendations, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 31)
      - Letters of Recommendation, 1979-1984 (Box 11, Folder 42)
      - Letters of Recommendation (2 folders), 1980-1986 (Box 12, Folder 4-5)
- Series III: Studies & Proposals, 1967-1984, n.d.
  Series III: Studies & Proposals, 1967-1984, n.d., includes three subseries. Subseries A: Student & Faculty Studies & Proposals, 1977-1982, n.d., includes reports, proposals, and studies with which Burchard was involved as a participant, consultant, or had some oversight as a professor. This subseries is in alphabetical order by folder title.
  Subseries B: Pre-Planning & Preliminary Reports, 1976-1982, includes material surrounding the general campus planning discussions at VPI at the time, as well as documents relating to specific locations and buildings. This subseries is in chronological order.
  Subseries C: Grant Applications, 1967-1984, consists of papers and files relating to research and applications for grants in which Burchard was involved. This subseries is in chronological order.
  - Subseries A: Students & Faculty Studies & Proposals, 1977-1982, n.d.
    - Consultant Report: Proposal for a PhD Program in Architecture, University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Proposals (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Faculty Proposals: Professor G. Day Ding (2 folders) (Box 12, Folder 17-18)
    - Guide to Faulty Presentations, Publications, Research, & Consulting, 1977-1982 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Student project, likely created by one of Burchard's students during his tenure at Virginia Tech (Folder 4)
    - Student Reports & Studies (5 folders) (Box 12, Folder 10-14)
    - VPI Master Plans (Folder 9)
  - Subseries B: Pre-Planning & Preliminary Reports, 1976-1982
    - Alternative Conceptual Campus Planning Study, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Basic Program of Space Requirements, Department of Chemistry, VPI, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Carneal & Johnson Campus Master Plan Study, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Chemistry Building Infill Planning (4 folders), 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 21-24)
    - Statements of Qualification, 1980-1982 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - VPI Preliminary Planning Studies (2 folders) (Box 12, Folder 27-28)
  - Subseries C: Grant Applications, 1967-1984
    - Proposal for Esso Education Foundation Grant, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - VPI: Grant Applications, 1969-1984 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Series IV: Publications & Reports, 1938-1987, n.d.
  Series IV: Publications & Reports, 1938-1987, n.d., contains nine subseries. Subseries A: Publications about Schools/School Buildings, 1941-1969, includes materials collected by Burchard as research for designs. Burchard designed several schools while working for the A. M. Kinney during this time. Folders in this subseries are in alphabetical order by title.
  Subseries B: Government Publications, 1969-1980, consists of two folders of United States government publications relating to architecture and design. This subseries is in chronological order.
  Subseries C: Reports & Design, Education & the Architecture Profession, 1966-1978, includes several catalogs from learning institutions, as well as multiple folders of reprints, reports, individual articles, and single issues of publications. This subseries is in chronological order.
  Subseries D: Building Design & City Planning, 1968-1987, includes publications relating to aspects of design, urban planning, city planning, and landscape design. This subseries is in chronological order.
  Subseries E: Virginia Tech Publications, 1964-1980, contains published reports, journals, and other items produced by the College of Architecture and the university at large. This subseries is in chronological order.
  Subseries F: Conferences & Seminars, consists of programs, conference proceedings, and other materials produced as a result of conferences, seminars, and other professional events. This subseries is in chronological order.
  Subseries G: Popular/Commercial Periodicals, 1938-1979, includes single articles, usually removed from popular magazines, relating to aspects of architecture and design. In addition, there are a few full issues of architectural journals and popular magazines. This subseries is in chronological order.
  Subseries H: Academic Journals, 1940-1989, n.d., contains single issues and runs of academic journals in the architecture field. Some include notes, marginalia, or other markings by Burchard. In addition, there are publications that specifically contain articles by Burchard or about him, and there is one folder of award excerpts removed from publications. This subseries is in chronological order with undated materials at the end.
  Subseries I: Newspapers, Clippings, & Tear Sheets, 1938-1983, has individual articles removed from periodicals, newspaper articles, and collections of clippings on architects (Burchard included) or architecture topics. Some materials contain marginalia and notes by Burchard. This subseries is in chronological order with undated materials at the end.
  - Subseries A: Publications about Schools/School Buildings, 1941-1969
    - Ministry of Education, Building Bulletin, 1949-1951 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Reports from Facilities Laboratories (2 folders), 1960-1962 (Box 13, Folder 2-3)
    - Schools and School Design, 1948-1969 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Schools and School Design (2 folders), 1960-1969 (Box 13, Folder 5-6)
  - Subseries B: Government Publications, 1969-1980
    - US Government Publications (2 folders), 1969-1980 (Box 13, Folder 7-8)
  - Subseries C: Reports & Design, Education & the Architecture Profession, 1966-1978
    - Architecture Education & Profession (6 folders), 1966-1978 (Box 13, Folder 9-14)
    - Modulus, UVa School of Architecture, Journal Design Education Symposium, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Rock Candy Mountain Learning/Education Catalog, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Whole Earth Catalog, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Subseries D: Building Design & City Planning, 1968-1987
    - Urban Design, City Planning, & Landscape (2 folders), 1968-1987 (Box 13, Folder 16-17)
  - Subseries E: Virginia Tech Publications, 1964-1980
    - Virignia Tech Publications (4 folders), 1964-1980 (Box 13, Folder 18-21)
  - Subseries F: Conferences & Seminars
    - Conferences & Seminars (4 folders) (Box 13, Folder 22-25)
  - Subseries G: Popular/Commercial Periodicals, 1938-1979
    - Arts & Architecture: The Gropius Symposium, May 1952 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Life (Double Issue on Picasso), 1969 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Periodicals, Single Issues (4 folders), 1938-1979 (Box 14, Folder 4-7)
    - Progressive Architecture (3 folders), 1954-1967 (Box 14, Folder 1-3)
  - Subseries H: Academic Journals, 1940-1989, n.d.
    - Marked Publications & Articles, 1940-1949 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Unmarked Publications & Articles, 1940-1949 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Academic Journals, Single Issue (3 folders), 1941-1983 (Box 14, Folder 9-11)
    - PLAN: Architecture Students Association Journal, 1948-1950 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Award Excerpts from Publications, 1954-1959 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Marked Publications & Articles, 1960-1989 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Unmarked Publications & Articles, 1960-1970 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Unmarked Publications & Articles, 1980-1989 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Charles Burchard Project Publications (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Publications and Articles mentioning Charles Burchard (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Subseries I: Newspapers, Clippings, & Tear Sheets, 1938-1983
    - Newspaper Clippings on Charles Burchard, 1944-1971 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Newspaper Clippings on Projects, 1947-1964 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Architectural Record: Today's House Client Is Practical, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Articles about Marcel Breuer, 1954, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Progressive Architecture, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Design of the School of Architecture Building at the University of Manitoba, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Architecture Forum: 100 Largest Architectural Firms in the U.S, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Articles and Tear Sheets--Projects by Burchard (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Marked Newspaper Articles (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Unmarked Newspaper Articles (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Series V: Personal Papers, 1935-1989, n.d.
  Series V: Personal Papers, 1935-1989, n.d., contains four subseries. Subseries A: Personal Papers, 1935-1989, n.d., consists of subject files, research files, and personal documents. Materials in this subseries are organized into sub-subseries by use/type of document (educational/professional, family/personal, financial, photographs, and travel). Each sub-subseries is arranged in chronological order.
  Subseries B: General Correspondence, 1939-1989, includes a group of Burchard's correspondence with family, friends, and professional colleagues (Sub-subseries 1: General Correspondence), as well as a group of correspondence kept by topic (Sub-subseries 2: Correspondence by Topic). Sub-subseries 2: Correspondence by Topic contains letters to and from organizations, clients, publishers, and other university administrators. Sub-series are arranged in alphabetical order by title. Materials in each sub-subseries are arranged in chronological order.
  Subseries C: Correspondence with Individuals, 1939-1989, consists of letters between Burchard and a specific correspondent OR between Burchard and others about a specific person/project. This subseries often includes materials surrounding well-known architects or firms, especially the work of Walter Gropius. Materials in this subseries are arranged alphabetically by the last name of the correspondent/subject.
  Subseries D: Certificates, 19271971, contains baptism and confirmation certificates from Charles Burchard, as well as honorary and fraternity related certificates and awards. This subseries is in chronological order.
  - Subseries A: Personal Papers, 1935-1989, n.d.
    - Sub-subseries 1: Education & Professorial
      - Harvard GSD: Application for Admission, 1939 (Box 14, Folder 28)
      - Registrations (2 folders), 1946-1963 (Box 14, Folder 29-30)
      - Resume, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 32)
      - State Registration, Rosters, & Rule Books, 1958-1963 (Box 14, Folder 33)
      - Alumni Materials, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Awards & Honors, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - University Distinguished Achievement Award, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Introspection, April 26, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Memberships & Registrations (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - Resumes, Introductions, & Curriculum Vitae (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - Stationary (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Sub-subseries 2: Family & Personal
      - Furniture Catalogs & Textiles (2 folders), 1971-1983 (Box 14, Folder 35-36)
      - Charles & Helen Burchard: Will and Estate Plans, 1979-1982 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Medical Brochures & Benefits, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Miscellaneous: Brochures & Memos (Box 15, Folder 23)
      - Miscellaneous: Documents and Elon Yearbooks (2) (Box 15, Folder 24)
      - Helen Burchard (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Sub-subseries 3: Financial
      - Financial: Taxes & Loans, 1935-1941 (Box 14, Folder 27)
      - Furniture Purchases & Information, 1947-1987 (Box 14, Folder 31)
      - Monetary Donations, 1969-1980 (Box 14, Folder 34)
      - Flower Maintenance & Landscaping, 1985-1987 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Investments & Financial Transactions (2 folders) (Box 15, Folder 13-14)
    - Sub-subseries 4: Photographs
      - Photographs: Charles Burchard (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - Photographs: Miscellaneous People (Box 15, Folder 18)
      - Photographs: Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 19)
      - Photographs: Nexus Gallery Scuptures, Boston (Box 15, Folder 21)
      - Sculpture & Sculptor Prints (Box 15, Folder 20)
      - Salzburg, Austria, photograph (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Sub-subseries 5: Travel
      - London Trip (2 folders), 1978 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Advisory Council Trip to Germany, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Berlin Trip, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Travel Expenses & Records (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Subseries B: General Correspondence, 1939-1989
    - Sub-subseries 1: General Correspondence
      - Correspondence, 1939-1944 (Box 15, Folder 28)
      - Correspondence, 1944-1949 (Box 15, Folder 29)
      - Letters, London, 1950-1951 (Box 15, Folder 31)
      - Correspondence, 1950-1954 (Box 15, Folder 33)
      - Correspondence, 1955-1959 (Box 15, Folder 35)
      - Correspondence, 1960-1964 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence (2 folders), 1970-1974 (Box 16, Folder 7-8)
      - Correspondence (2 folders), 1975-1979 (Box 16, Folder 10-11)
      - Correspondence (3 folders), 1980-1984 (Box 16, Folder 15-17)
      - Correspondence, 1985-1989 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Sub-subseries 2: Correspondence by Topic
      - AIA Correspondence, 1975-1980 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Burchard House,Construction & Finishes, 1969-1971 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Book Reviews: Who's Who, 1946-1948 (Box 15, Folder 30)
      - Distinguished Building Awards Program, Chicago, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - College of Fellows Nomination, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Harvard: Architecture Association Correspondence, 1950-1951 (Box 15, Folder 32)
      - Harvard GSD Report, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Steven & Cathi House: Proposal, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 18)
      - MIT: Undergraduate Thesis Correspondence, 1938 (Box 15, Folder 26)
      - Owens, Corning Facility, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Publication Correspondence, 1939-1963 (Box 15, Folder 27)
      - Dean Julio San Jose, Memoranda & Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Dean Charles Steger, Memoranda & Correspondence, 1981-1989 (Box 16, Folder 20)
      - Teaching Leads: Correspondence, 1952-1968 (Box 15, Folder 34)
      - University Distinguished Professors Correspondence, 1979-1983 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - VPI College of Architecture, Dean Appointments, 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - US Federal Government, Legislative Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Subseries C: Correspondence with Individuals, 1939-1989
    - Herbet Agoos, 1953-1989 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Marcel Breuer (Box 16, Folder 35)